<documents>
<document>
<docID>2012022825466</docID>
<docDate>20120228</docDate>
<docSource/>
<docText>IBM Tivoli Management Software - Tivoli Stor FlashCopy ManagerTivoli Stor FlashCopy Manager. Restrictions: &#8226; Only available to businesses,   government agencies and academic institutions operating within the USA and ...
  
    Due to compliance-related export restrictions, we are only
    able to fulfill orders for organizations that have presence
    within either United States or Russia. Products, prices, and
    availability are subject to change without notice. All prices
    are in US dollars and do not include sales tax or freigh
    charges. State sales/use tax will be collected whenever
    required by federal laws. Freight charges may apply to
    hardware orders. Email or call us for an estimate.
  
</docText><Company>IBM Tivoli Management</Company>
<Company>IBM</Company>
<Company>Tivoli Stor FlashCopy ManagerTivoli Stor FlashCopy</Company>
<Company>Tivoli</Company>
<Person>Stor FlashCopy</Person>
<Location>Tivoli Stor FlashCopy ManagerTivoli Stor FlashCopy</Location>
<Location>Tivoli</Location>
<Location>USA</Location>
<Location>United States</Location>
<Location>United</Location>
<Location>Russia</Location>
<Function>Manager</Function>
</document>
</documents>