<documents>
<document>
<docID>2012022811320</docID>
<docDate>20120228</docDate>
<docSource/>
<docText>Review of Biblioth&#232;que Nationale de France, Site Tolbiac/Fran&#231;ois Mitterrand and other library/university reviews in ParisFrommer&#39;s review of Biblioth&#232;que Nationale de France, Site Tolbiac/Fran&#231;ois   Mitterrand in Paris. Get information about this attraction including applicable cost, ...
  
    Frommer's Star Ratings
  
  
    About Our System
  
  
    Frommer's ranks every hotel, restaurant, attraction, shop, and
    nightlife establishment it reviews for quality, value,
    service, amenities, and special features using a star-rating
    scale, an expression of the strong compare-and-contrast
    opinions that are a brand hallmark.
  
  
    Other ratings provide stars based primarily on price and
    amenities; the Frommer's star rating is meant to quantify the
    kind of intangible, experiential elements that help travelers
    make informed decisions.
  
  
    The "baseline" recommendation is zero stars--every hotel,
    restaurant, attraction, shop, and nightlife establishment that
    Frommer's chooses to review is recommended; otherwise, we
    simply wouldn't include it.
  
  
    
  
</docText><Person>Fran&#231;ois Mitterrand</Person>
<Person>Fran&#231;ois   Mitterrand</Person>
<Location>France</Location>
<Location>Tolbiac</Location>
<Location>Paris</Location>
</document>
</documents>